A Guide to the Richmond Renaissance Inc. Archives, 1956-1995
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series VII: Richmond Renaissance Inventory 1997
  - Regional Quarterly 1994 (Box A1)
  - The St. Louis Package (Box A1)
  - Kings Dominion 1994 (Box A1)
  - Harper's; Vol. 289, no. 132 (Box A1)
  - Historical Richmond Foundation News; Winter 1994 (Box A1)
  - Smith Travel Research 1994 (Box A1)
  - The Richmond Commercial Real Estate Market Review 1993-1994 (Box A1)
  - Viewpoint: Real Estate Value Trends 1994 (Box A1)
  - World's Fair 1993, 1996 (Box A1)
  - Regional System Plan Study for Eastern Va. 1994 (Box A1)
  - Governor's Task Force on Tourism 1994 (Box A1)
  - Downtown Richmond, Inc. 1994 (Box A2)
  - City of Richmond North Core Strategy; March 1994 (Box 2)
  - Travel Information 1990 (Box A2)
  - Blueprint for Sustainable Development of Va 1994 (Box A2)
  - Richmond Better Housing Coalition Annual Report 1994 (Box A2)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Park Annual Report 1993-1994 (Box A2)
  - Newspaper Articles (Disney America) 1993-1994 (Box A2)
  - Richmond National Battlefield Park; Feb. 1994 (Box A2)
  - Rountrey Letter; May 1994 (Box A2)
  - Richmond Renaissance Business Leaders Meeting 1994 (Box A2)
  - Metro View; Vol. 21 no. 8 (Box A2)
  - Image 87-88 (Box A2)
  - Richmond Attraction 1985-1986 (Box A2)
  - Richmond Riverfront Sculpture Competition 1986-1987 (Box A2)
  - State Arts Commission Grant (Box A2)
  - Circuit City Stores Inc. Annual Report 1994 (Box A2)
  - Travel Industry Employment of the U.S. Econ 1993 (Box A2)
  - Euralille 1995 (Box A2)
  - Downtown Richmond Development and Management 1993 (Box A2)
  - Black History Museum and Cultural Center, Inc.: City Ordinances and By-Laws (Box A2)
  - Black History Museum and Cultural Center, Inc.: Board of Trustees (Box A2)
  - Black History Museum and Cultural Center, Inc.: Letters of Transmittal (Box A2)
  - Black History Museum and Cultural Center, Inc.: City of Richmond Commission of Archival Review (Box A2)
  - Black History Museum and Cultural Center, Inc.: Szabo, Raymond (Box A2)
  - Black History Museum and Cultural Center, Inc.: Structural Plans (Box A2)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box A2)
  - Newsletter (Box A2)
  - Lease Agreement (Box A2)
  - City of Richmond Planning Commission (Box A2)
  - Finances (Box A2)
  - Overview (Box A2)
  - Dobbins, Albert (Box A2)
  - Preliminary Plans and Proposals (Box A2)
  - Black History Museum and Cultural Center, Inc.: Miscellaneous (Box A2)
  - Sixth Street Market Place (Box A2)
  - Parking Transportation 1985-1986 (Box A2)
  - Richmond Electric Street Car Proposal 1985-1987 (Box A2)
  - Small Business Financing 1983 (Box A3)
  - Marketing Analysis (Chesterfield, Hanover, Henrico, and Richmond); Jan. 1986 (Box A3)
  - Glenn Monigle and Association, Inc. (Box A3)
  - Public-Private Partnership: Education and Employment 1984-1986 (Box A3)
  - Downtown Richmond Small Business Proposal 1983-1986 (Box A3)
  - Public Relation 1985-1989 (Box A3)
  - Terry P. Cribbs 1987-1986 (Box A3)
  - Diamond Graphics 1986-1987 (Box A3)
  - Larry S. Pemberton 1985-1989 (Box A3)
  - Quick Print 1986-1987 (Box A3)
  - Credit Bureau of Richmond-Broad Street 1986 (Box A3)
  - A and E Supply Co., Inc. 1986-1988 (Box A3)
  - Anderson Printing 1986 (Box A3)
  - Best Sign System 1986-1988 (Box A3)
  - City of Richmond 1987 (Box A3)
  - J.T. Leasing 1986 (Box A3)
  - Lawler Ballard Advertising 1986-1987 (Box A3)
  - Manpower Incorporated 1986-1987 (Box A3)
  - Canal Walk Brick (misc.) 1986-1988 (Box A3)
  - Glave Newman Anderson-Gateway 1986 (Box A3)
  - John D. Hunt 1986 (Box A3)
  - Lambert Laminations 1986 (Box A3)
  - Walter S. Blake 1988 (Box A3)
  - C and P Telephone 1986-1989 (Box A3)
  - Thomas Martinson 1988 (Box A3)
  - Richmond Marriott 1988 (Box A3)
  - Willie Redd 1987-1988 (Box A3)
  - Stull and Lee 1988 (Box A3)
  - Thomas and Meaus Associates 1988 (Box A3)
  - W. Davis Van Bakergem 1988 (Box A3)
  - Virginia Power 1989 (Box A3)
  - Apple Pie Graphics 1989 (Box A3)
  - Hood Temple AME Zion Church 1989 (Box A3)
  - Audio/Visual Equipment 1988 (Box A3)
  - Mailing List 1987-1989 (Box A3)
  - Newsletter 1987-1989 (Box A3)
  - Fundraising Breakfast 1989 (Box A3)
  - Board Meetings 1989 (Box A3)
  - The Aarow Group 1987-1988 (Box A3)
  - Sculpture Competition 1987-1989 (Box A3)
  - Hammer, Siler George and Associates 1986 (Box A3)
  - Res. Development (misc.) 1986 (Box A3)
  - Professional P.R. Services 1987 (Box A3)
  - Wilbur Smith and Associates 1985-1986 (Box A3)
  - Policeman Service 1988 (Box A3)
  - Lease/Rentals 1989 (Box A3)
  - Temporary Receptionist 1989 (Box A3)
  - Aetna Life Insurance and Annuity Company 1989 (Box A3)
  - Dedication 1987-1988 (Box A3)
  - Accounting 1989 (Box A3)
  - Data Processing 1989 (Box A3)
  - Bike Courier Services 1989 (Box A3)
  - Health Insurance (Box A3)
  - Caterer 1989 (Box A3)
  - Membership Dues 1988-1989 (Box A3)
  - Shipping Charges 1989 (Box A3)
  - B. Richard Glasscock 1989 (Box A3)
  - Plants 1989 (Box A3)
  - Coffee Supplies 1989 (Box A3)
  - Employer's Federal Tax Return 1989 (Box A3)
  - Federal Tax 1987-1989 (Box A3)
  - State Tax 1988-1989 (Box A3)
  - Real Estate 1989 (Box A3)
- Riverfront
  - Belle Isle/BIB Improvements 1991 (Box A4)
  - Crowder Work 1991 (Box A4)
  - Old B1 Re. All Study/ULI 1986-1991 (Box A4)
  - Math Sciences Center Contract 1986-1988 (Box A4)
  - Recreational Access Fund (Correspondence, Application, etc.) 1985-1986 (Box A4)
  - State Grants 1986 (Box A4)
  - Locomotive, Flywheel, Artifacts 1986-1987 (Box A4)
  - Virginia Power Work 1986-1987 (Box A4)
  - Haxall Canal Walk Brown's Island Improvement-Plan 1987 (Box A4)
  - Tredegar Street 1985-1988 (Box A4)
  - General City Insurance Certificate 1987 (Box A4)
  - Direct Mail 1986 (Box A4)
  - Raft Race 1985-1986 (Box A4)
  - Outdoor Adventure Day 1985 (Box A4)
  - JRD: Down By the Riverside 1986 (Box A4)
  - River Festival 1986-1987 (Box A4)
  - Decert/Turnover of SBA 503 Waves 1989 (Box A4)
  - Coleman P. Perrin, Inc. Progress Payments 1987 (Box A4)
  - Requisitions-Progress Payments 1986 (Box A4)
  - Clearances/Review/Permits (Canal Walk) 1986 (Box A4)
  - Sales Tax/Conservation 1986 (Box A4)
  - Legal Agreement Canal Walk 1986 (Box A4)
  - Plat Survey Information 1986 (Box A4)
  - Canal Walk Budget/Source and use of Cash Flow 1985-1987 (Box A4)
  - Construction Contact-Administration 1986-1987 (Box A4)
  - Canal Walk Construction Contract Originals 1986-1987 (Box A4)
  - Budget/Source to Use/Cash Flow 1988-1990 (Box A5)
  - Proposal and Construction Contract Negotiation 1986 (Box A5)
  - Drafting of Construction Contract 1985-1986 (Box A5)
  - Canal Walk Cost Estimates Opportunities 1986 (Box A5)
  - Banners 1987-1988 (Box A5)
  - Purchase Order Voucher 1990-1992 (Box A5)
  - Statue 1987 (Box A5)
  - Benches 1987 (Box A5)
  - Helicopter Pad 1986-1988 (Box A5)
  - Construction Contract-Bid Process Canal Walk/Brown's Island 1986 (Box A5)
  - Brown's Island (photo of flood); June 1972 (Box A5)
  - Bridge 1986-1988 (Box A5)
  - Bridge: Part B 1986-1988 (Box A5)
  - Historic Markers 1986 (Box A5)
  - Part D-Submissions (Box A5)
  - KIOSK Design 1986 (Box A5)
  - Whitman/HOH Contract Mgt. 1986-1987 (Box A5)
  - Whitman-Requardt HOH Contract Canal Walk 1985-1986 (Box A5)
  - ASLA-Canal Walk (Brown's Island-Preliminary Design Effort) 1985 (Box A5)
  - Tredgar St.-Misc. 1991 (Box A5)
  - Belle Isle-General 1986-1990 (Box A5)
  - Tredegar Signage 1989-1990 (Box A5)
  - Brown's Island (early) Cost and Design (Abbott) 1982 (Box A5)
  - Legal Easement AG Brown's Island Walkway (Box A5)
  - Paul B. Williams, Inc. (Box A6)
  - Automatic Data Processing 1989 (Box A6)
  - Pitney Bowes 1989 (Box A6)
  - Deferred Compensation 1988-1989 (Box A6)
  - Fringe Benefits 1988-1989 (Box A6)
  - Reimbursements 1988-1989 (Box A6)
  - Sodas 1989 (Box A6)
  - Tax Deferred Annuity 1988-1989 (Box A6)
  - Ribbons/Quietprinter 1988-1989 (Box A6)
  - Rent 1988-1989 (Box A6)
  - Office Supplies 1989 (Box A6)
  - Moveable Feast 1989 (Box A6)
  - Metro Chamber 1989 (Box A6)
  - Parking Staff 1989 (Box A6)
  - Replenish Petty Cash 1989 (Box A6)
  - Rental/Meta. 1989 (Box A6)
  - Replenish Postage 1989 (Box A6)
  - Plant Maintenance 1989 (Box A6)
  - Annuity Life Insurance 1989 (Box A6)
  - TSA-R.E. Olson (Box A6)
  - IDS 1987-1989 (Box A6)
  - CLT, Jr. 1986-1989 (Box A6)
  - Albert G. Dobbins, III 1983-1988 (Box A6)
  - Sherri Jones 1987-1988 (Box A6)
  - Magazine Subscriptions 1987-1989 (Box A6)
  - Touche Ross 1986-1989 (Box A6)
  - Virginia Realty 1989 (Box A6)
  - Virginia Downtown Development Association 1989 (Box A6)
  - Peter Wong and Associates 1986-1987 (Box A6)
  - Xerox Cooperation 1988-1989 (Box A6)
  - Keith-Fabry Reproductions 1989 (Box A6)
  - Photos 1985-1989 (Box A6)
  - Travel/Hotel Accomodations 1988-1989 (Box A6)
  - Miscellaneous (Box A6)
  - Transit Development Program for the Urbanized Area 1989-1993 (Box A7)
  - Department of Social Services: Neighborhood Assistant Act Application 1990 (Box A7)
  - Local Initiatives Support Cooperation 1991 (Box A7)
  - Committee Report to The Richmond Renaissance Executive Committee (Box A7)
  - Touche Ross: Greater Richmond Transit Co. Management Letter; October 1988 (Box A7)
  - Type I Market Report; June 1989 (Box A7)
  - Portland Development Commission 1986-1987 (Box A7)
  - Richmond Renaissance: Keeping Up Appearance and Script (Box A7)
  - Demand For Rental Housing; Sept 1986 (Box A7)
  - Foran and Greer Inc. 1986-1987 (Box A7)
  - The Housing Market For Downtown Richmond/Adjacent Neighborhoods; Virginia Housing Partnership Fund 1991 (Box A7)
  - Committee Report to the Richmond Renaissance; September 1986 (Box A7)
  - Hammer, Siler, George and Associates: Economic Development Consultant 1990 (Box A7)
  - Central Business District Route Analysis; May 1985 (Box A7)
  - Multi-Family Loan Program (Box A7)
  - Hutton and Williams: Sale of Stock to Chesterfield County; June 1989 (Box A7)
  - Downtown Residential Development Committee; March 1986 (Box A7)
  - The Governor's Plan on State Housing Policy Development and Organizational Streamlining; December 1990 (Box A7)
  - Cultural Link Trolley Study; December 1987 (Box A7)
  - Resolution: Election of the Board of Directors; March 1986 (Box A7)
  - Inter-Department Correspondence; March 1987 (Box A7)
  - Minutes of Board Directors 1987-1988 (Box A7)
  - Operating Report 1987-1989 (Box A7)
  - U.S. Department of Transportation 1989 (Box A7)
  - GRTC Financial Statements 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  - GRTC Board Meetings 1987-1989 (Box A7)
  - Downtown Housing 1984-1990 (Box A7)
  - Housing: Low and Moderate Income 1986-1988 (Box A7)
  - SMH: Cultural Link 1987 (Box A7)
  - Dec. 21 Board Meeting and Slide Presentation 1987-1988 (Box A7)
  - AV: Accomplishments and Challenges 1985 (Box A7)
  - Conflict and Intersection Along the James River Canal (slides) (Box A)
  - Virginia Housing Foundation (Box A)
  - AV Equipment Manuals (Box A7)
  - Culture Link Donation Letters and Account Information (Box A7)
  - Miscellaneous (Box A7)
  - Southeastern Institute of Research, Inc.; March 1983 (Box A8)
  - Housing Resources Directory 1988 (Box A8)
  - A Strategy for Action for Downtown Richmond 1976-2000 (Box A8)
  - The Third and Clay Building (Box A8)
  - Center for Public Affairs; April 1987 (Box A8)
  - Living Downtown; June 1987 (Box A8)
  - Community Development Guide; March 1987 (Box A8)
  - New Homes for New York Neighborhoods; Oct. 1984 (Box A8)
  - A Proposed Strategy for Organizing, Staffing, and Funding a Renaissance in Tourism and Convention Development in the Richmond, Virginia Area; Sept. 1982 (Box A8)
  - Tobacco Row Development 1986-1988 (Box A8)
  - Richmond Downtown Transportation Center, Executive Summary; July 1987 (Box A8)
  - Metropolitan Richmond Chamber of Commerce (Box A8)
  - Market Analysis; January 1986 (Box A8)
  - Glen Monigle and Associates Inc. 1987 (Box A8)
  - South of James Redevelopment Committee (Box A8)
  - Center for Black Enterprises; September 1989 (Box A8)
  - Preliminary Feasibility Analysis of a Rental Rehabilitation Project 4th and Grace Street; December 1989 (Box A8)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000 1988 (Box A8)
  - CDC (Community Development Cooperation) 1985-1988 (Box A8)
  - National Congress for Community Economic Development 1981 (Box A8)
  - The Beacon Council (Miami, Florida) 1987 (Box A8)
  - Electric Streetcar 1988-1990 (Box A8)
  - Jackson Place 1988-1989 (Box A8)
  - National Endowment for the Arts/Design Arts Program Grants Data Base (Box A8)
  - Jackson Center Office Building Richmond, Virginia 1991 (Box A8)
  - Travel in Virginia Annual Report 1988 (Box A9)
  - Transit Development Program for the Richmond Urbanized Area 1991-1995; September 1989 (Box A9)
  - Handbook of Architectural Design Competition 1988 (Box A9)
  - Design Competition Manual 1980, 1982, 1988 (Box A9)
  - Banking Information 1987-1988 (Box A9)
  - Brochures 1987-1988 (Box A9)
  - Downtown Plan Issues 1983 (Box A9)
  - Market and Operating Analysis Marketplace Cinema; November 1986 (Box A9)
  - Jackson Center (Box A9)
  - Visitor Center 1987 (Box A9)
  - Newspaper Articles: Downtown Richmond 1987-1989 (Box A9)
  - Hanover and Henrico County 1987 (Box A9)
  - Central Atlanta Civic Development, Inc. (Box A9)
  - City of Sunfish Lake (Box A9)
  - City Planning 1987 (Box A9)
  - Valentine Museum 1987 (Box A9)
  - Halcyon Ltd. (Box A9)
  - Notes; December 1989 (Box A9)
  - Miscellaneous 1987-1988 (Box A9)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000: Technical Report; May 1988 (Box A9)
  - Sixth Street Marketplace: Debt Restructure; Dec. 1986 (Box A9)
  - Sixth Street Marketplace: Financing, Land Assemblage, Development and Operating Documents (Box A9)
  - Center for Black Enterprises 1990 (Box A9)
  - Asset Managemtent Introduction: The City of Richmond, Va; March 1988 (Box A10)
  - Downtown Richmond (slides) (Box A10)
  - Sixth Street Marketplace Analysis and Proposal (Goodman Segar Hogan) (Box A10)
  - Sixth Street Marketplace Blueprints (Box A10)
  - Good Government Award Brochures; June 1991 (Box A10)
  - The Curator; Vol. 4; March, April, May 1990 (Box A10)
  - Richmond Renaissance Downtown Residential Development Committee; September 1986 (Box A10)
  - Richmond Renaissance Incorporated Meeting of the Board of Directors; June 1991 (Box A10)
  - Richmond Renaissance 9th Year Committee; December 1991 (Box A10)
  - The Virginia Biotechnology Research Park Project 1990 (Box A10)
  - Summary of Retail Projects: LaSalle Partners (Box A10)
  - Statement of Qualifications: Polytech, Inc. (Box A10)
  - Halcyon Ltd.; May 1988 (Box A10)
  - 6th Street Transaction Agreement 1988 (Box A10)
  - Neptune Seafork Inc.; August 1988 (Box A10)
  - The Webb Companies; May 1988 (Box A10)
  - Jacobs, Visconis and Jacobs Co. (Box A11)
  - 6th Street Marketplace Memorandums to Bob Barron 1988 (Box A11)
  - Tower City Center (Box A11)
  - Canal Walk Banners (Box A11)
  - Photos (Box A11)
  - Multi Media 1993 (Box A11)
  - Disney 1993 (Box A11)
  - Gaming 1993 (Box A11)
  - Land Ownership 1989 (Box A11)
  - Improvements Since Agnes 1991-1992 (Box A11)
  - Tom Moore and Governor's Task 1994 (Box A11)
  - Chadbourne Correspondence 1993 (Box A11)
  - Chris Chadbourne 1992-1993 (Box A11)
  - Consultant Interview; August 1993 (Box A11)
  - Charrette Information 1993 (Box A11)
  - Intercept Surveys 1993 (Box A11)
  - Clarion Reports 1993 (Box A11)
  - Clairon Correspondence 1993-1994 (Box A11)
  - Clairon 1993 (Box A11)
  - Hard Road to Glory 1992-1993 (Box A11)
  - Trigg Shipyard Walkway (Box A11)
  - Trigg Shipyard H20 View (Box A11)
  - Chimborazo Hospital (Box A11)
  - Chimborazo Floor Plan (Box A11)
  - Clarion Assoc. Inc. Qualifications (Box A11)
  - RIVA Correspondence 1993 (Box A11)
  - RIVA Reports 1993 (Box A11)
  - RIVA 1993 (Box A11)
  - RIVA Focus Groups 1991-1993 (Box A11)
  - TDA 1993 (Box A11)
  - AA Sports Hall of Fame (Box A11)
  - New Images-CATD (Box A11)
  - Misc. Consultants 1993 (Box A11)
  - CAA Interviews 1993 (Box A11)
  - Good Copies (Box A11)
  - Civil War Museum (Box A11)
  - Evacuation Fire (Box A11)
  - SMC Documents 1993-1994 (Box A11)
  - Virginia's Tourism Development Plan; Final Draft; November 1994 (Box A11)
  - Seminar Readings 1992-1993 (Box A11)
  - Church Hill PH Park (Box A11)
  - Conserving Richmond's Battlefields; October 1990 (Box A11)
  - For Marks Building (Box A11)
  - For Sherman (Box A11)
  - Fire/Atlanta (Box A11)
  - Floor Plan (Box A11)
  - H Skramstad 1993 (Box A11)
  - Ben Lawless 1993 (Box A11)
  - Trigg Shipyard Plan (Box A11)
  - Confederate Navy Patrick Harris Proposal; September 1991 (Box A11)
  - National Museum of Civil War 1993 (Box A11)
  - Fall of Richmond Fire 1993-1994 (Box A11)
  - Crestar 1993-1994 (Box A11)
  - Consultants (Box A11)
  - Richmond Theme 1994 (Box A11)
  - Budgets 1993 (Box A11)
  - A Guide to Business Incentives; April 1993 (Box A11)
  - A Guide to State Government Services for Small Businesses; September 1991 (Box A11)
  - A Proposed Strategy for Organizing, Staffing, and Funding a Renaissance in Tourism and Convention Development in the Richmond, Va. Area; September 1985 (Box A11)
  - The Valentine; September 1994 (Box A12)
  - National Center for Civil War and Reconstruction 1994 (Box A12)
  - Options for the Philip Morris Property (Box A12)
  - Department of Transportation 1993 (Box A12)
  - Youth Services System Resources Manual (Box A12)
  - Integration of Vocation and Academic; May 1993 (Box A12)
  - School to Work Transition in Washington 1993 (Box A12)
  - Excerpts from Report of Inquiry Group on VSAF Loans; April 1992 (Box A12)
  - Raleigh for the People (Box A12)
  - The Fourth R Workforce Readiness 1987 (Box A12)
  - Success for All in a New Century; November 1989 (Box A12)
  - Commission for Educational Excellence; June 1991 (Box A12)
  - Reports and Recommendation; April 1994 (Box A12)
  - Recrafting the Business of Schooling 1993 (Box A12)
  - The Business Roundtable; May 1993 (Box A12)
  - Virginia Riverboat Council; August 1994 (Box A12)
  - Glen Monigle and Associates, Inc. (Box A12)
  - Jackson Center, Downtown Richmond (Box A12)
  - Downtown Richmond Photographs (Box A12)
  - Financial Documents 1993 (Box A12)
  - The Jackson Historian District (Box A13)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000; May 1988 (Box A13)
  - The Return of Livable City: Learning from America's Best (Box A13)
  - Partnership for the 1990's (Box A13)
  - Culture Link Tour Brochure (Box A13)
  - Jackson Ward (Stickers) (Box A13)
  - Jackson Ward Vision 2000: Technical Appendix; May 1988 (Box A13)
  - Jackson Ward: Al Dobbins 1988 (Box A13)
  - Committee Report to the Richmond Renaissance Executive Committee; September 1986 (Box A13)
  - The Third and Clay Building (Box A13)
  - Board Street Residential Study 1986 (Box A13)
  - Brook Crossing Commercial Center: Existing Conditions (Box A13)
  - Brook Crossing Commercial Center: Neighborhood Profile (Box A13)
  - Type I Market Report (Market Area) (Location); June 1986 (Box A13)
  - Summary of Environmental Assessment: Maggie Walker; January 1982 (Box A13)
  - General Development Plan: Maggie Walker; January 1982 (Box A13)
  - Downtown Data Book 1987 (Box A13)
  - Request for Design-Build Proposal; April 1987 (Box A13)
  - Central Wards: Neighborhood Planning Study 1973 (Box A13)
  - Broad Street Residential Study: Living Over the Store; May 1986 (Box A13)
  - Summary: Findings of Broad/Grace Street Retail District Analysis 1986 (Box A13)
  - Downtown Richmond Plan (Box A13)
  - Broad Street Facade Renovation Project 1985 (Box A13)
  - Broad Street Facade Renovation Project; March 1985 (Box A13)
  - Memorandum: Findings of Broad Street Retail Analysis 1986 (Box A13)
  - A Proposed Strategy for Organizing, Staffing and Funding a Renaissance in Tourism and Convention (Box A13)
  - Development in the Richmond, Virginia Area; Sept 1982 (Box A13)
  - Fundamentals of Municipal Bonds 1990 (Box A14)
  - The City Themed as Destination (Phase I: Feasibility); December 1993 (Box A14)
  - Preliminary Story Lines and Themes and Preliminary Capital and Operation Budgets for the City as Attraction 1993 (Box A14)
  - CATD Charrette Info. 1988 (Box A14)
  - CATD Reports 1993 (Box A14)
  - Entrepreneurship Video 1994 (Box A14)
  - CATD Transportation 1993 (Box A14)
  - CATD Financing 1994 (Box A14)
  - Downtown Richmond Inc. Board of Directors 1992-1993 (Box A14)
  - CATD Responsibilities 1993 (Box A14)
  - Newspaper Article to Frank-to Notebooks 1992-1994 (Box A14)
  - Report; March 1994 (Box A14)
  - Transportation-Georgetown Loop 1984 (Box A14)
  - Themes 1993 (Box A14)
  - CATD Market Research 1993 (Box A14)
  - Bank Street 1993 (Box A14)
  - Harvard Business Review 1994 (Box A14)
  - Frank Jewell 1991-1994 (Box A14)
  - Valentine Museum Final Report 1993 (Box A14)
  - Tourism 1994 (Box A14)
  - Richmond Themed as Destination 1988-1994 (Box A14)
  - Executive Summary of the City of Richmond 1994 (Box A14)
  - Newsletter Photos/Layouts (Box A15)
  - Canal Walk Photos (Box A15)
  - Richmond One to One 1993 (Box A15)
  - Accelerated Schools Project 1990 (Box A15)
  - Manual for In-Service Education (Box A15)
  - Discipline and Truancy Improvement Team; July 1992 (Box A15)
  - Student Assessment Committee; November 1992 (Box A15)
  - Education Committee 1992 (Box A15)
  - Staff Development Committee; November 1992 (Box A15)
  - School Assessment Committee 1992-1994 (Box A15)
  - Curriculum and Mentoring Committee 1992-1994 (Box A16)
  - Pre-School Committee 1990-1993 (Box A16)
  - Structure Committee 1991-1992 (Box A16)
  - Reducing Learning Barriers Committees 1992-1993 (Box A16)
  - Technology Committee 1991-1992 (Box A16)
  - Staff Assessment Committee 1990-1992 (Box A16)
  - Disposition and Development Agreement; June 1984 (Box A17)
  - Richmond Festival Marketplace Partnership; December 1985 (Box A17)
  - Task Force Training for Richmond Tomorrow 1990 (Box A17)
  - Metropolitan Visitors Orientation Center (Box A17)
  - Gateway Project Plan April 15, 1985 (Box A17)
  - Gateway Project Plan July 13, 1985 (Box A17)
  - Gateway Project Architects October 15, 1984 (Box A17)
  - Richmond Community Development Corporation (Box A17)
  - Really Richmond: Media at Large December 6, 1985 (Box A17)
  - Richmond: Continental Cable 1986 (Box A17)
  - Apple Pie Graphics 1985 (Box A17)
  - Syndereb Inc. (Box A17)
  - Hardwicke Ekstrom and Associates; July 1983 (Box A17)
  - Proposal for: Downtown Richmond Master Planning Study; October 1984 (Box A17)
  - 2nd Street Development Project; June 1983 (Box A17)
  - Revitalization Plan for the Second Street Business Area; December 1983 (Box A17)
  - Vincent Ciulla Design (Box A17)
  - Economic Impact of a Proposal Regional Visitor Orientation and Information Center in the Richmond, Virginia Metro Region 1985 (Box A17)
  - Proposed Boundaries: Jackson Ward and Historic District (Box A17)
  - A Commercial Revitalization Plan for the Second Street Commercial Area Richmond, Virginia; March 1981 (Box A17)
  - Ownership Guide (Box A17)
  - The Programmatic and Thematic Content for a Proposed Orientation and Information Center; April 1986 (Box A17)
  - Casella and Associates; February 1989 (Box A17)
  - Georgia Trend; August 1989 (Box A17)
  - Armanda Hoffler 1988 (Box A17)
  - Adrian Development Inc. 1990 (Box A18)
  - Glenn Monigle and Associates, Inc. (Box A18)
  - Statement of Qualification 1988 (Box A18)
  - Vision 2000 Office 1988-1992 (Box A18)
  - Jackson Ward: Community Development Corporation 1988 (Box A18)
  - Jackson Center Leasing 1989 (Box A18)
  - Prang Estates (Box A18)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank of Atlanta; July 1990 (Box A18)
  - Thomas and Means Associates Inc.; November 1987 (Box A18)
  - The Virginia Statute for Religious Freedom 1986-1988 (Box A18)
  - Profile 1988 (Box A18)